Guide to the Duncan McNaughton Papers M1459
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 3: Writings/Publications/Drafts
  - Valparaiso (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Love Triumphant. Meditations on William Shakespeare's The Sonnets (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Love Triumphant final draft given to typist 1972 (Box 30, Folders 4-5)
  - Corrections to A New Variorum Edition of Shakespeare's The Sonnets (Box 30, Folders 6-7)
  - Corrections to A New Variorum Edition of Shakespeare's The Sonnets (Box 31, Folders 1-4)
  - "In Limine": poem drafts + Corrections by Duncan McNaughton/Dario Villa (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - "Introduction to American Poetry" Fall 1987 UCSC (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - CPF (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - 'Aql 1981. M CPF (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Ms. of selected Poetry and Prose (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Sonny Boy (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Love for Sale (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Drafts and Scrawls [1982-1983] Berkeley (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Verse and Prose 1980-81 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Interview/Price and Smith in Mike and Dale's 1998 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Prose Must be as of Wind Laughing (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Wind Laughing Legible Xerox of Complete 1st typescript (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Wind Laughing A book by D. McNaughton (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Plays: Mary's, Dogs (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Morning (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Nerval's Necktie (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - A Collage Cover for The Pilot (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - La Rosita (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Natal Chart (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts of remarks at Intersection April 1983 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - The Pilot (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - The Pilot Sept. 1986 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - The Pilot Notebook Sept. 1986 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - The Pilot Sept. 1986 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - The Pilot (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Paper written for Creeley's class at Buffalo (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - McNaughtons First Poem ca. 1961- Provincetown (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Shao's dream 1979 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - 24 Mar. 1988 RD reading at Bolinas for D McN w/ note from J. [Kyger?] (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - CPF typescript 1986 (Box 34, Folders 5-7)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Manuscripts drafts of pieces in CPS 1979 [Bolinas] (Box 34, Folders 9-11)
  - La Rosita Ms. After love for Sale begin Sept. 1984 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Copy Mother Magazine #8 1967 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Patzcuaro Joanne Kyger (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Patzcuaro drafts (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Patzcuaro Material (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Villa Book 2 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Fathar one (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Fathar 2 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Fathar III (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Fathar for (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Fathar 5 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Fathar sixty-six (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Fathar Zayin (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Shit on My Shoes (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Another set of circumstance. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - The Wrapped Church (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Valparaiso (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Dream (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - The Pilot (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Kicking The Feather (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Sumeriana (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Dario Villa (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Patzcuaro (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - A Passage of Saint Devil (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Philipp Schiemann (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - 2 CD's I'm a Poet (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Dario Villa (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Venus Material (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Venus Material (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Venus Material (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Fathar Material (Box 37, Folders 6-7)
  - Broadsides and Postcards 70s-90s (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Love Triumphant 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folders 2-4)
  - La Rosita Ms. After Love for Sale begin Sept. 1984 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Mother - side one magnetic tape (Box 39)
  - Mother - side two magnetic tape (Box 39)
  - Mother number 9 Record (Box 39)
  - 1) Terry Bell (Bolinas) A. Calligraphy - (color photocopy) - "In Whoese Circuity the Heart's Complete" from The Pilot. 1991. B. Poster for New College of California reading 22 Feb. 1976 [E. Dorn, M. McClure, L. MacAdams, D. McNaughton] 2) Joanne Kyger/Donald Guranich - 1997 - broadside "The Dying Plum" from Kicking the Feather 3) McNaughton/Peter Downsbrough - 1970s broadside - ed. Louis Patler 4) Poster for McNaugthon lecture 19 Mar. '79 at Capilano College, N. Vancouver, BC - "another set of circumstance: Poetry + historical Geography." via Pierre Coupey (Flat-box 40, Folder 1)
  - Sonny Boy (27 p. holograph of typescript) (Box 41, Folder 1)